So we have seen CloudFormation and Beanstalk,
but now let's talk about CodeDeploys.
So CodeDeploys is also a way
for us to deploy our application automatically.
Now the difference that CodeDeploy is a bit more permissive.
It doesn't need to be using Beanstalk or CloudFormation.
This is completely independent.
So with CodeDeploy,
We have our application,
it's in version one,
and we want you to upgrade it into version two.
So CodeDeploy will find a way for us to do this.
So CodeDeploy works with two things.
It works with EC2 instances.
And so you can have many EC2 instances being upgraded
from V1 to V2,
but it also works with On-Premises Servers.
So if you have Servers On-Premises,
and you want to help them upgrade from version one
to version two for your applications,
it is possible to do it with CodeDeploy.
So CodeDeploy, If you look at it,
it is what's called a hybrid service
because it works both for On-Premises,
and for EC2 instances.
So CodeDeploy really allows you to work
with any kind of servers,
but you must provision the servers ahead of time.
Okay, It's up to you.
And you must configure them
to install the CodeDeploy agent
that will be assisting you to do these upgrades.
So CodeDeploy is quite a handy service on AWS.
It really allows people to do the transition
from On-Premises to AWS by using the same way
to deploy the application
either with your On-Premise Servers,
or your EC2 instances.
And it is an advanced service,
so I can't really demo it for you,
but what you need to remember is that it allows you to
upgrade both your EC2 instances, applications,
and your On-Premises Servers applications
from version one to version two,
automatically from a single interface.
So hope that was helpful.
And I will see you in the next lecture.